<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WIFI Analyzer: WIFI Passwords</string>
    <string name="f1">Wifi Analyzer- Home &amp; Office Wifi Security has been called one of the most impressive router network utilities on the Store. Wifi optimizer helps you to optimize your wifi network and suggests you the strongest wifi password with a Wifi password generator.</string>
    <string name="nw">Network Analyzer and Wifi Scanner supports you to Optimize your WiFi network by examining nearby WiFi networks, calculating their signal strength as well as identifying crowded channels. It will recommend the best channel for your network. WiFi Monitor Analyzer gives you the most beneficial optimization information to support decrease interference and increase connection speed and stability. WiFi explorer also suggests the best channel and place for your wifi network. Now using this wifi optimizer and wifi scanner you can optimize wifi networks and estimate their signal strength, estimate distance, wifi channels, and much more.</string>
    <string name="c105">Now you can use it for Wi-Fi signal strength or discover the strongest signal spot in your house or office. This wifi finder &amp; network analyzer offers useful information about wireless signals around you. WiFi signal analyzer is a new way to analyze and optimize your WiFi, Turn your android device into WiFi analizer!</string>
    <string name="c102">Wifi Analyzer - Wifi scanner app is used to Optimize and Analyze WiFi Networks by testing WiFi Signal, Crowded signal, Scanning signal strength and Channel rating. WiFi Data Analyzer shows WiFi channels around you. It can support you to find a less crowded channel for your wireless router. With Wifi Analyzer you can Expand the network performance via analyzing and monitoring your WiFi networks.</string>
    <string name="c104">Scan Wifi network and select the strongest signal wifi connection with wifi signal analyzer and enjoy the wifi at high speed. The stronger your wifi the higher the internet speed you get. Wifi optimizer helps you to optimize your wifi network and suggests you the strongest wifi password with a Wifi password generator. Wifi scan or analyze to identify easily &amp; quickly and see how many devices are connected to your wifi router.</string>
    <string name="c1">speed up and setup networks. Helps to quickly detecting any computer net problems, ip address and boosting wifi and mobile connection performance. This is a must-have app for all home wireless router users, IT experts and network administrators.</string>
    <string name="c14">It is equipped with a fast wifi device discovery tool, including all the LAN device\'s addresses, manufacturers and names. Further, Network Analyzer contains standard net diagnostic tools such as ping, traceroute, port scanner, DNS lookup, and whois. Finally, it shows all neighbouring wi-fi networks together with additional details such as signal strength, encryption and router manufacturer to help discovering the best channel for a wireless router.</string>

</resources>